A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Historical Files, SG 1, Series 1 FA389
Rockefeller Archive Center
- San Carlos Apache Tribe (Apache Junction, Arizona), January 21, 1977-April 19, 1977 (Box 70, Folder 1213)
- Santamaria, J. N. (Vincent's Hospital, Victoria, Australia), June 16, 1972-July 5, 1972 (Box 70, Folder 1214)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Sap-Sce), October 4, 1946-January 21, 1981 (Box 70, Folder 1215)
- Sarrel, Phillip M. (Yale University, School of Medicine), April 16, 1971-June 25, 1975 (Box 70, Folder 1216)
- Saskatchewan Hospital, September 11, 1951-July 20, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 1217)
- University of Saskatchewan, November 13, 1951-September 10, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 1218)
- Saslow, George, December 27, 1951-April 23, 1957 (Box 71, Folder 1219)
- Saturday Review, June 3, 1968-April 29, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 1220)
- Saunders, Lyle, September 19, 1951-September 7, 1961 (Box 71, Folder 1221)
- Saunders, Richard H., Jr., April 4, 1968-May 8, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 1222)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Scha-Schm), September 24, 1948-June 3, 1981 (Box 71, Folder 1223)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Schn-Schw), June 1, 1950-November 3, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 1224)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Sci-Scy), January 2, 1948-October 15, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 1225)
- Office of Scientific and Development, August 3, 1941-November 13, 1945 (Box 71, Folder 1226)
- University of Scranton, July 1, 1977-August 3, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 1227)
- Scripps Clinic and Research Foundation (California), February 9, 1970-March 17, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 1228)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Sea-Sei), October 31, 1950-September 26, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 1229)
- Seale, John R., May 11, 1958-May 21, 1959 (Box 71, Folder 1230)
- Sears, Robert E., December 11, 1952-December 15, 1953 (Box 72, Folder 1231)
- Seattle City Council, February 7, 1974-June 24, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 1232)
- Seattle Pacific College, October 31, 1956-November 7, 1956 (Box 72, Folder 1233)
- Seattle University, August 23, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1234)
- Second International Conference on Temporal Lobe, May 3, 1955-July 19, 1955 (Box 72, Folder 1235)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Sel-Sey), January 23, 1950-December 11, 1980 (Box 72, Folder 1236)
- Seton Hall College of Medicine, January 6, 1956-June 15, 1965 (Box 72, Folder 1237)
- Sex Education (Commonwealth Fund Program - Richard A. Chilgren), August 25, 1976-September 10, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 1238)
- Sex Information and Education Council of United States, April 9, 1969-December 10, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 1239)
- Sex Information and Education Council of United States, April 9, 1969-December 10, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 1240)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Sha), April 19, 1951-April 9, 1981 (Box 72, Folder 1241)
- Shannon, James A., June 14, 1976-October 5, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 1242)
- Shaw, Dennis F. (Keble College, England), November 13-20, 1969 (Box 72, Folder 1243)
- Cross Reference Sheets (She), November 24, 1944-December 11, 1980 (Box 72, Folder 1244)
- Shepherd, Michael, February 13, 1957-April 30, 1957 (Box 73, Folder 1245)
- Sheps, Jack, October 1, 1953 (Box 73, Folder 1246)
- University of Sherbrooke, December 1-3, 1964 (Box 73, Folder 1247)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Shi-Shy), December 7, 1950-March 7, 1981 (Box 73, Folder 1248)
- Shimkin, Demitri, September 19, 1971-November 9, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 1249)
- Shuler, Virginia, November 18, 1957 (Box 73, Folder 1250)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Sia-Sil), March 22, 1951-March 24, 1981 (Box 73, Folder 1251)
- Silver, George A. (Center for International Health Policy Studies), April 17, 1958-February 21, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 1252)
- Silver, George A. (Center for International Health Policy Studies), April 17, 1958-February 21, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 1253)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Sim), February 9, 1951-November 11, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 1254)
- Simmons College (Boston, Massachusetts), November 15, 1971-September 14, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 1255)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Sin-Siz), September 5, 1950-April 2, 1981 (Box 73, Folder 1256)
- Six Year Medical School Program, July 7-17, 1975 (Box 73, Folder 1257)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Sk-Smil), December 14, 1950-November 4, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 1258)
- Skidmore College, December 8, 1953-July 29, 1964 (Box 73, Folder 1259)
- Cross Reference Sheets - Smith (A-E), May 21, 1951-September 19, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 1260)
- Smith, Barry C., September 30, 1947-February 9, 1961 (Box 74, Folder 1261)
- Smith, Barry C. (Retirement and Successor), July 16, 1946-January 31, 1949 (Box 74, Folder 1262)
- Smith College, September 26, 1952-July 15, 1980 (Box 74, Folder 1263)
- Smith, Datus C., Jr., October 24, 1969-October 17, 1977 (Box 74, Folder 1264)
- Cross Reference Sheets - Smith (F-K), April 9, 1951-January 4, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 1265)
- Smith, Geddess, June 16, 1953-March 13, 1963 (Box 74, Folder 1266)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Smith (L)-Smy), February 21, 1944-December 1, 1980 (Box 74, Folder 1267)
- Smith, Lloyd H., July 17, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 1268)
- Smithsonian Institution, February 8, 1967-November 14, 1980 (Box 74, Folder 1269)
- Smuts, Alice (Ann Arbor, Michigan), September 8, 1977 (Box 74, Folder 1270)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Sn), May 21, 1951-March 24, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 1271)
- Snoke, Albert and Parnie, January 11, 1974-September 28, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 1272)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Soa-Sol), August 1, 1949-November 17, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 1273)
- Sobel, Alma (Mrs. A. Watson), September 10, 1973-October 2, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 1274)
- Social Development Corporation (Ralph Showalter), May 29, 1967-September 27, 1971 (Box 74, Folder 1275)
- Social Science Research Council, April 6, 1954-April 22, 1960 (Box 74, Folder 1276)
- Society for Health and Human Values, May 28, 1971-October 24, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 1277)
- Society for Research in Child Development, April 2-9, 1951 (Box 75, Folder 1278)
- Society for the Family of Man, September 25, 1968-August 20, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 1279)
- Society of Biological Psychiatry, March 29, 1951-June 17, 1951 (Box 75, Folder 1280)
- Solomon Fuller Institute (Cambridge, Massachusetts), July 2, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 1281)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Som-Soz), 1943-June 30, 1981 (Box 75, Folder 1282)
- Somers, Anne, September 18, 1964-July 23, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 1283)
- Soskin, William F., January 13, 1959-November 9, 1960 (Box 75, Folder 1284)
- University of South Alabama, April 1, 1970-December 9, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 1285)
- University of South Dakota, November 21, 1967-February 20, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 1286)
- Southeast Michigan Council of Governments, December 5, 1968 (Box 75, Folder 1287)
- University of Southern California, July 16, 1955-September 18, 1980 (Box 75, Folder 1288)
- University of Southern California, July 16, 1955-September 18, 1980 (Box 75, Folder 1289)
- University of Southern California (Bartz, Robert V.), April 7, 1973-July 3, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 1290)
- University of Southern California (Human Resources Research Center - Donald E. Yett), September 18, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 1291)
- Southern Illinois University (School of Medicine), July 16, 1976-October 27, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 1292)
- Southern Medical Association, August 3, 1953-December 21, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 1293)
- Southern Methodist University, February 26, 1973-March 1, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 1294)
- Southern Pacific Memorial Hospital, Inc. (Harkness Community Hospital), April 18, 1968 (Box 75, Folder 1295)
- Southern Regional Council, Inc., September 22, 1973-September 10, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 1296)
- Southern Regional Education Board, August 24, 1954-October 29, 1981 (Box 75, Folder 1297)
- Southwest Health Care Corporation (New Mexico), March 31, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 1298)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Spa-Spe), September 12, 1951-August 19, 1980 (Box 75, Folder 1299)
- Special Commission on Internal Pollution (Rebecca Rainsbury, London), January 19, 1973 (Box 76, Folder 1300)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Spi-Sr), January 26, 1950-March 16, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 1301)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Staa-Stap), November 14, 1950-May 5, 1980 (Box 76, Folder 1302)
- Stanford University (School of Medicine), March 21, 1949-January 7, 1980 (Box 76, Folder 1303)
- Stanford University (School of Medicine), March 21, 1949-January 7, 1980 (Box 76, Folder 1304)
- Stanford University (School of Medicine), March 21, 1949-January 7, 1980 (Box 76, Folder 1305)
- Stanford University (School of Medicine - Addition to Research Laboratory), August 6-9, 1971 (Box 76, Folder 1306)
- Stanford University (School of Medicine - Education Exchange with British Honduras), December 4-29, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 1307)
- Stanford University Hospital (Physicians' Assistants), December 1, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 1308)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Star-Stay), January 26, 1951-March 6, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 1309)
- State of the Union (President's Address), February 3, 1971 (Box 76, Folder 1310)
- State University of New York (Albany), May 21, 1968-May 22, 1973 (Box 76, Folder 1311)
- State University of New York (Buffalo), October 25, 1968-April 19, 1973 (Box 77, Folder 1312)
- State University of New York (New York City), May 1, 1953-February 16, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 1313)
- State University of New York (Stony Brook - Training in Social Biology, Eli A. Rubinstein), April 23, 1973-August 14, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 1314)
- State University of New York (Syracuse), October 19, 1951-December 4, 1975 (Box 77, Folder 1315)
- State University of New York (Upstate Medical Center), December 8, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 1316)
- State University System of Florida, October 27, 1972-December 4, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 1317)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Stea-Stei), December 18, 1948-January 30, 1981 (Box 77, Folder 1318)
- Stead, Eugene A., Jr., June 30, 1975-April 9, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 1319)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Stel-Ster), April 5, 1951-September 15, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 1320)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Ste), September 16, 1946-August 26, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 1321)
- Stevens, Kingley M., December 26, 1972-January 31, 1973 (Box 77, Folder 1322)
- Stevenson, Ian, December 29, 1949-April 19, 1960 (Box 77, Folder 1323)
- Stewart, Gerald, October 11, 1951-November 7, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 1324)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Sti-Stj), May 21, 1951-March 19, 1981 (Box 77, Folder 1325)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Sto), March 17, 1950-July 15, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 1326)
- Stockholm University, January 24, 1952 (Box 78, Folder 1327)
- Stokes, Thomas Land and Levi Old (Norfolk, Virginia), December 12-20, 1977 (Box 78, Folder 1328)
- Stone, Alan A., June 28, 1968-July 2, 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1329)
- Storey, Patrick (Continuing Medical Education), September 11, 1967-January 12, 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1330)
- Stover, G. Franklin, April 22-29, 1957 (Box 78, Folder 1331)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Stra-Stre), March 8, 1951-February 5, 1981 (Box 78, Folder 1332)
- Strand, James E. (American Hospital Association), January 27, 1969 (Box 78, Folder 1333)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Stri-Stu), August 4, 1950-March 25, 1981 (Box 78, Folder 1334)
- Struthers, Robert R., June 22, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 1335)
- Student American Medical Association, December 2, 1970-January 14, 1972 (Box 78, Folder 1336)
- Study of the Full-time System, December 15-20, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 1337)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Sua-Sun), November 20, 1950-September 8, 1978 (Box 78, Folder 1338)
- Summerskill, John, May 6, 1970-August 18, 1970 (Box 78, Folder 1339)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Sup-Swa), January 26, 1949-October 2, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 1340)
- Superbooks, July 30, 1958-October 15, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 1341)
- Survey of Commonwealth Fund Grants, June 26, 1958-August 27, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 1342)
- Survey of Commonwealth Fund Grants (Iago Galdston), November 6, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 1343)
- Survey of Commonwealth Fund Grants (Peter Lee), September 4, 1958-April 23, 1959 (Box 78, Folder 1344)
- Survey of Commonwealth Fund Grants (Peter Lee), September 4, 1958-April 23, 1959 (Box 78, Folder 1345)
- Survey of Commonwealth Fund Grants (Peter Lee), October 7, 1959-November 12, 1959 (Box 79, Folder 1346)
- Sutherland Productions, Inc. (Sutherland Learning Associates), March 19, 1970-January 31, 1978 (Box 79, Folder 1347)
- Swampscott Conference in Behavioral Science (Oliver Cope), June 5, 1967-November 7, 1967 (Box 79, Folder 1348)
- Swampscott Conference in Behavioral Science (Oliver Cope), June 5, 1967-November 7, 1967 (Box 79, Folder 1349)
- Swampscott Conference in Behavioral Science (Oliver Cope), June 5, 1967-November 7, 1967 (Box 79, Folder 1350)
- Swanson Center for Nutrition (Omaha, Nebraska), September 2, 1976 (Box 79, Folder 1351)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Swe-Sy), June 27, 1950-July 28, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 1352)
- Sydney University, July 10, 1956-June 6, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 1353)
- Syracuse University, January 20, 1947-February 23, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 1354)
- Syracuse University Research Corporation, January 9-28, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 1355)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Tab-Tax), October 15, 1951-July 21, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 1356)
- Taft Information System (Washington, D.C.), August 27, 1971-July 20, 1976 (Box 79, Folder 1357)
- Tavistock Clinic (London), December 6, 1962-March 10, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 1358)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Tay), December 17, 1940-October 3, 1980 (Box 80, Folder 1359)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Te), July 27, 1946-February 19, 1981 (Box 80, Folder 1360)
- Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association of America-College Retirement Equities Fund, October 12-29, 1976 (Box 80, Folder 1361)
- Temple University, February 1, 1954-October 18, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 1362)
- Temple University (School of Medicine - Capital Grants), May 31, 1955-December 13, 1976 (Box 80, Folder 1363)
- Temple University (School of Medicine - Capital Grants), May 31, 1955-December 13, 1976 (Box 80, Folder 1364)
- Temple University (School of Medicine - Health Science Center), January 23, 1968-October 19, 1976 (Box 80, Folder 1365)
- Tennessee Public Health Association, October 19, 1977-December 9, 1977 (Box 80, Folder 1366)
- University of Tennessee, December 1, 1958-November 14, 1980 (Box 80, Folder 1367)
- Texas Medical Center (Institute of Religion), January 11, 1960-January 4, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 1368)
- Texas Technical University (Lubbock), June 13, 1969-March 3, 1980 (Box 80, Folder 1369)
- University of Texas (Galveston), December 9, 1974-June 20, 1979 (Box 80, Folder 1370)
- University of Texas (Houston), June 29, 1951-January 28, 1974 (Box 81, Folder 1371)
- University of Texas (M. D. Anderson Hospital and Tumor Institute), January 2, 1969-January 14, 1971 (Box 81, Folder 1372)
- University of Texas (Medical School at San Antonio), February 29, 1968-January 22, 1980 (Box 81, Folder 1373)
- University of Texas (Southwestern Medical School), August 1, 1969-October 9, 1974 (Box 81, Folder 1374)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Tha-Thi), June 4, 1952-November 10, 1980 (Box 81, Folder 1375)
- Theology-Medicine, December 2, 1971 (Box 81, Folder 1376)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Thom), November 3, 1949-March 27, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 1377)
- Thomas, Charles C., April 28, 1950 (Box 81, Folder 1378)
- Mary Thompson Hospital, July 26, 1957-August 20, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 1379)
- Thompson, John D. (Hospital Ward Book, Yale University Press), April 20, 1972-June 12, 1972 (Box 81, Folder 1380)
- Thomson, Captane P., February 11, 1958 (Box 81, Folder 1381)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Thon-Thy), April 14, 1951-July 17, 1980 (Box 81, Folder 1382)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Ti-Too), May 11, 1950-November 14, 1980 (Box 81, Folder 1383)
- Tobin, Charles E., February 26, 1968-November 12, 1968 (Box 81, Folder 1384)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Top-Toz), December 6, 1950-October 20, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 1385)
- Topiwala National Medical College, March 14, 1952-April 5, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 1386)
- University ot Toronto, April 12, 1951-April 7, 1977 (Box 81, Folder 1387)
- Tougaloo College (Mississippi), January 21, 1974-January 15, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 1388)
- Towe, Charlotte, February 7-27, 1951 (Box 81, Folder 1389)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Tra-Tre), September 17, 1951-February 7, 1980 (Box 81, Folder 1390)
- Traut, Marjorie, January 2-15, 1975 (Box 82, Folder 1391)
- Tresan, David I., November 1, 1961-March 2, 1962 (Box 82, Folder 1392)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Tri-Try), April 11, 1950-March 25, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 1393)
- Trinity College (Hartford, Connecticut), July 31, 1968-June 10, 1977 (Box 82, Folder 1394)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Tu), June 1, 1949-April 9, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 1395)
- Tufts University (School of Dental Medicine), April 13, 1966-January 11, 1957 (Box 82, Folder 1396)
- Tufts University (School of Medicine), June 30, 1976-April 14, 1977 (Box 82, Folder 1397)
- Tufts University (School of Medicine - New England Medical Center), May 1, 1945-May 15, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 1398)
- Tufts University (School of Medicine - New England Medical Center), May 1, 1945-May 15, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 1399)
- Tulane University, October 17, 1949-August 16, 1977 (Box 82, Folder 1400)
- Tulane University, October 17, 1949-August 16, 1977 (Box 82, Folder 1401)
- Tulane University School of Public Health and Tropical Medicine - Family Health and Population Division), June 3, 1968-March 23, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 1402)
- Tuskegee Institute, October 10, 1952-August 9, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 1403)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Tv-Tw), June 27, 1951-July 16, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 1404)
- Twentieth Century Fund, November 23, 1966-February 5, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 1405)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Uc-Unit), February 21, 1951-November 21, 1979 (Box 83, Folder 1406)
- Union for Experimenting Colleges and Universities, July 15, 1971-May 1, 1976 (Box 83, Folder 1407)
- Union Theological Seminary, November 14, 1973-December 6, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 1408)
- Cross Reference Sheets - United, March 19, 1951-July 15, 1980 (Box 83, Folder 1409)
- United Air Lines, March 23-30, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 1410)
- United Church Boards (Mobil Oil and Supply to Rhodesia), August 3-8, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 1411)
- United Community Services, September 21-24, 1956 (Box 83, Folder 1412)
- United Health Foundations, Inc., September 19, 1962-July 11, 1969 (Box 83, Folder 1413)
- United Hospital Fund of New York, July 1, 1963-May 4, 1978 (Box 83, Folder 1414)
- United Mine Workers of America, December 3, 1952-May 11, 1959 (Box 83, Folder 1415)
- United Mine Workers of America, December 3, 1952-May 11, 1959 (Box 83, Folder 1416)
- United Nations, December 7, 1972-December 30, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 1417)
- United Nations (Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization), August 7, 1950-December 7, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 1418)
- United Negro College Fund, Inc., July 31, 1968-June 18, 1975 (Box 83, Folder 1419)
- United States Advisory Commission on Educational Exchange, March 21, 1952-July 26, 1954 (Box 83, Folder 1420)
- United States Army Medical Research and Development Command, July 30, 1959-January 4, 1960 (Box 83, Folder 1421)
- United States Children's Bureau Migrant Workers, January 22, 1954-February 1, 1954 (Box 83, Folder 1422)
- United States Department of Health, Education and Welfare (Public Health Service), June 16, 1953-October 21, 1963 (Box 83, Folder 1423)
- United States Department of Health, Education and Welfare (Public Health Services - Conferences), March 21, 1956-October 29, 1959 (Box 84, Folder 1424)
- United States Department of Justice (Immigration and Nationality Act), January 19, 1953-September 23, 1954 (Box 84, Folder 1425)
- United States Department of Labor, June 12, 1958-August 7, 1958 (Box 84, Folder 1426)
- United States Office of Education (Foundations Meeting), April 21, 1967-January 21, 1969 (Box 84, Folder 1427)
- United States Public Health Service, February 2, 1951-June 1, 1970 (Box 84, Folder 1428)
- United States Public Health Service (Communicable Disease Center, Atlanta, Georgia), June 10, 1953-September 24, 1957 (Box 84, Folder 1429)
- United States Public Health Service (National Institute of Mental Health), July 8, 1951-August 14, 1961 (Box 84, Folder 1430)
- United States Public Health Service (National Institute of Mental Health), July 8, 1951-August 14, 1961 (Box 84, Folder 1431)
- United States Public Health Service (National Institute of Mental Health), July 8, 1951-August 14, 1961 (Box 84, Folder 1432)
- United States Senate, January 14, 1955-March 23, 1961 (Box 84, Folder 1433)
- United Student Aid Funds (New York), April 6-12, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 1434)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Univ-Uz), March 13, 1947-October 12, 1981 (Box 84, Folder 1435)
- Universidad Autonoma de Guadalajara, March 14, 1962-May 10, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 1436)
- Universidad Autonoma de Guadalajara, March 14, 1962-May 10, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 1437)
- Universidad Autonoma de Guadalajara, March 14, 1962-May 10, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 1438)
- University City Science Center (Sheila Clibbon and Marvin Sachs), October 19, 1972 (Box 84, Folder 1439)
- University College (Ibadan, Nigeria) - School of Nursing, July 10, 1956 (Box 85, Folder 1440)
- University College of Rhodesia and Nyasaland, September 23, 1958-April 30, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 1441)
- University College London, November 19, 1964-September 28, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 1442)
- University of the West Indies, January 13, 1960-February 2, 1977 (Box 85, Folder 1443)
- Upchurch, Ouida C., August 21, 1971-August 16, 1972 (Box 85, Folder 1444)
- Urban Housing, December 11, 1964 (Box 85, Folder 1445)
- Urban Problem, June 26, 1968-September 22, 1970 (Box 85, Folder 1446)
- Ursin, Holger (University of Bergen), October 21, 1967-December 15, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 1447)
- University of Utah, November 15, 1951-April 27, 1976 (Box 85, Folder 1448)
- University of Utah, November 15, 1951-April 27, 1976 (Box 85, Folder 1449)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Vaa-Vand), September 11, 1951-March 25, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 1450)
- Valenti, Dr., April 18, 1957 (Box 85, Folder 1451)
- Vanderbilt Clinic of the Presbyterian Hospital (New York), April 18, 1972 (Box 85, Folder 1452)
- Vanderbilt University (School of Medicine), April 24, 1950-December 7, 1955 (Box 85, Folder 1453)
- Vanderbilt University (School of Medicine), February 16, 1956-February 5, 1981 (Box 86, Folder 1454)
- Vanderbilt University (School of Medicine), February 16, 1956-February 5, 1981 (Box 86, Folder 1455)
- Vanderbilt University (School of Medicine), February 16, 1956-February 5, 1981 (Box 86, Folder 1456)
- Vanderbilt University (School of Medicine), February 16, 1956-February 5, 1981 (Box 86, Folder 1457)
- Vanderbilt University (School of Medicine - Capital Grants), September 1, 1955-November 17, 1955 (Box 86, Folder 1458)
- Vanderbilt University (School of Nursing), January 24, 1951-July 30, 1959 (Box 86, Folder 1459)
- Vanderbilt, William H., February 23, 1973-September 30, 1976 (Box 86, Folder 1460)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Vane-Vaz), January 2, 1951-December 14, 1978 (Box 86, Folder 1461)
- Van Sandt, M. M., January 5, 1951-May 7, 1952 (Box 86, Folder 1462)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Ve-Vic), September 11, 1951-August 12, 1980 (Box 86, Folder 1463)
- Vellore Christian Medical College, August 14, 1956-February 17, 1958 (Box 86, Folder 1464)
- Venereal Disease Rate, June 1, 1970 (Box 86, Folder 1465)
- Vermont (Department of Health - Anthony Robbins), October 30, 1974-May 2, 1975 (Box 86, Folder 1466)
- University of Vermont, May 9, 1961-May 17, 1976 (Box 86, Folder 1467)
- University of Vermont, May 9, 1961-May 17, 1976 (Box 86, Folder 1468)
- University of Vermont (Allied Health Professions), October 3, 1967-April 18, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1469)
- Veterans Administration (Department of Medicine and Surgery), April 22, 1977 (Box 87, Folder 1470)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Vid-Vog), January 19, 1948-April 29, 1980 (Box 87, Folder 1471)
- Virginia State Department of Health, August 12, 1952-September 23, 1952 (Box 87, Folder 1472)
- University of Virginia (School of Law), January 11, 1949-July 26, 1979 (Box 87, Folder 1473)